and Aunt Claudia went to get me a little wall
of present
hand or that
oh my dear
thank you from the heart saw
it's a little dirty here
more ah
thank you
imagine
take the day to do something I'm already up
long time ago
good day to you
day 31
the deg BAK
I can't use my time anymore
effort to earn less
I have to use this time
effort to earn more
I will put together 1 New business plan
Wherever
You are now in danger
pay close attention to what I'm going to explain to you
and clean showcase is high effort etique from below
does not compensate for the effort because you earn little
good eliminates
to chair
effort is high
the ticket is average
good eliminates
if it's with dog
effort is low
and at most you get an average ticket
eliminates
pick up flyer
medium to high effort and ticket is medium
good eliminates
place truffles at commercial points
Trojan horse style
low effort
high tour ticket
continues
but having 1 lace is just shit
what i need to do
I eliminated a showcase
opened space
I earn twenty percent of my time
I eliminated the chairs
I open space
I save time
I stopped walking a dog
I open space
I save time
I stopped delivering pamphlet
I open space and save time
this initial plan of phase one
the only thing I'll go on
is to use twenty percent
of my time and effort
to get eighty percent of my result
only it's called parito law
still i need
do more things
phase one is like a dog when he pees on the pole
he has to mark territory
I created relationship
confidence
expansion of places and Network
what happens to all of it
Cayon build a strong shield
when you build a strong shield
product and service comes out and the brand is the one that stays
and if the brand becomes
i can now charge more
charge more by doing that there
no no no
no no
I need to find something I can get
have 1 low effort
and earn more and thus have much more money like
find something that I am good
this something that I am good and people recognize me
so
EU with you
have 1 smaller effort and 1 bigger ticket
I'm calling that there will be people talking
oh but i'm not good at anything
stop seeing meme and start studying
is on
that's why we don't leave the place
because we don't stop to think about planning
into something strategic
а ти о